Honey just got funny.
Bee Movie is a family, animation, adventure film directed by Simon J. Smith.
Benson, a recent college graduate who wants more out of his life than making honey, decides to sue
the human race after learning about the exploitation of bees at the hands of mankind.
What will happen next?
Barry B. Benson (voice), played by Jerry Seinfeld.
Vanessa Bloome (voice), played by Renée Zellweger.
Adam Flayman (voice), played by Matthew Broderick.
Ken (voice), played by Patrick Warburton.
Layton T. Montgomery (voice), played by John Goodman.
Mooseblood (voice), played by Chris Rock.
Bee Movie is a 2007 American animated satirical comedy film directed by Simon J.
Smith and Steve Hickner, and written by Jerry Seinfeld,
Spike Feresten, Barry Marder, and Andy Robin.
Produced by DreamWorks Animation and Columbus 81
Productions, it stars Seinfeld and Renée Zellweger.
The film centers on Barry B.
Benson (Seinfeld), an anthropomorphic honey bee who tries to sue the human race for exploiting bees after
learning from his new florist friend Vanessa Bloome (Zellweger) that humans sell and consume honey.
Bee Movie premiered in New York City on October 25, 2007, and was released in
theaters in the United States on November 2 by Paramount Pictures.
It grossed $293.5 million worldwide on a budget of $150 million.
It received mixed reviews from critics, who praised its humor and voice
cast but criticized its plot and lack of originality.
Nevertheless, it has since gained a cult following, partly driven by internet memes of the film shared on
social media, which most often lampoon its surreal premise, script and celebrity cameos.
The film explores themes of factory worker, airplane, court, tennis, florist.
The tone is lighthearted.